{"text":"function helloWorld() \n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  print(:)\n}\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  print(\"\")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  print(\"H\")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  print(\"HE\")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  print(\"HEL\")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  print(\"HELL\")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  print(\"HELLO\")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  print(\"HEL\")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  print(\"HE\")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  print(\"H\")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  print(\"He\")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  print(\"Hel\")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  print(\"Hell\")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  print(\"Hello\")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  print(\"Hello \")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  print(\"Hello W\")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  print(\"Hello Wo\")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  print(\"Hello Wol\")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  print(\"Hello Wolr\")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  print(\"Hello Wolrd\")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  print(\"Hello Wol\")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  print(\"Hello Wo\")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  print(\"Hello Wor\")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  print(\"Hello Worl\")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  print(\"Hello World\")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  print(\"Hello World!\")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n}\nd\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n}\nde\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n}\ndef\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n}\ndef \nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n}\ndef g\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n}\ndef ge\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n}\ndef get\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n}\ndef get_\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n}\ndef get_T\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n}\ndef get_Ty\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n}\ndef get_Tyy\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n}\ndef get_Typy\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n}\ndef get_Typey\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n}\ndef get_Tyy\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n}\ndef get_Ty\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n}\ndef get_y\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n}\ndef get_ty\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n}\ndef get_tyy\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n}\ndef get_typy\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n}\ndef get_typey\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n}\ndef get_type*y\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n}\ndef get_type()y\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n}\ndef get_typey\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n}\ndef get_typy\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n}\ndef get_tyy\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n}\ndef get_ty\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n}\ndef get_y\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n}\ndef gety\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n}\ndef gey\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n}\ndef gy\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n}\ndef y\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n}\ndefy\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n}\ndey\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n}\ndy\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n}\ny\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n}\ny\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nd\n}\ny\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nde\n}\ny\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\ndef\n}\ny\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\ndef \n}\ny\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\ndef g\n}\ny\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\ndef ge\n}\ny\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\ndef get\n}\ny\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\ndef get_\n}\ny\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\ndef get_t\n}\ny\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\ndef get_ty\n}\ny\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\ndef get_typ\n}\ny\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\ndef get_type\n}\ny\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\ndef get_type()\n}\ny\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\ndef get_type(v)\n}\ny\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\ndef get_type(va)\n}\ny\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\ndef get_type(var)\n}\ny\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\ndef get_type(vara)\n}\ny\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\ndef get_type(varai)\n}\ny\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\ndef get_type(varaib)\n}\ny\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\ndef get_type(varaibl)\n}\ny\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\ndef get_type(varaible)\n}\ny\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\ndef get_type(varaible);\n}\ny\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\ndef get_type(varaible);\n\n}\ny\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\ndef get_type(varaible);\n\n\n}\ny\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\ndef get_type(varaible);\n\nr\n}\ny\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\ndef get_type(varaible);\n\nre\n}\ny\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\ndef get_type(varaible);\n\nree\n}\ny\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\ndef get_type(varaible);\n\nrete\n}\ny\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\ndef get_type(varaible);\n\nretue\n}\ny\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\ndef get_type(varaible);\n\nreture\n}\ny\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\ndef get_type(varaible);\n\nreturne\n}\ny\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\ndef get_type(varaible);\n\nreturn e\n}\ny\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\ndef get_type(varaible);\n\nreturn te\n}\ny\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\ndef get_type(varaible);\n\nreturn tye\n}\ny\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\ndef get_type(varaible);\n\nreturn type\n}\ny\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\ndef get_type(varaible);\n\nreturn typee\n}\ny\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\ndef get_type(varaible);\n\nreturn typeoe\n}\ny\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\ndef get_type(varaible);\n\nreturn typeofe\n}\ny\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\ndef get_type(varaible);\n\nreturn typeof()e\n}\ny\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\ndef get_type(varaible);\n\nreturn typeof(v)e\n}\ny\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\ndef get_type(varaible);\n\nreturn typeof(va)e\n}\ny\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\ndef get_type(varaible);\n\nreturn typeof(var)e\n}\ny\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\ndef get_type(varaible);\n\nreturn typeof(vara)e\n}\ny\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\ndef get_type(varaible);\n\nreturn typeof(varai)e\n}\ny\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\ndef get_type(varaible);\n\nreturn typeof(varaib)e\n}\ny\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\ndef get_type(varaible);\n\nreturn typeof(varaibl)e\n}\ny\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\ndef get_type(varaible);\n\nreturn typeof(varaible)e\n}\ny\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\ndef get_type(varaible);\n\nreturn typeof(varaible);e\n}\ny\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\ndef s(varaible);\n\nreturn typeof(varaible);e\n}\ny\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\ndef sh(varaible);\n\nreturn typeof(varaible);e\n}\ny\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\ndef sho(varaible);\n\nreturn typeof(varaible);e\n}\ny\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\ndef show(varaible);\n\nreturn typeof(varaible);e\n}\ny\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\ndef showa(varaible);\n\nreturn typeof(varaible);e\n}\ny\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\ndef showal(varaible);\n\nreturn typeof(varaible);e\n}\ny\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\ndef showall(varaible);\n\nreturn typeof(varaible);e\n}\ny\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\ndef showallT(varaible);\n\nreturn typeof(varaible);e\n}\ny\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\ndef showallTy(varaible);\n\nreturn typeof(varaible);e\n}\ny\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\ndef showallTyp(varaible);\n\nreturn typeof(varaible);e\n}\ny\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\ndef showallType(varaible);\n\nreturn typeof(varaible);e\n}\ny\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\ndef showallTypes(varaible);\n\nreturn typeof(varaible);e\n}\ny\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\ndef showa\\llTypes(varaible);\n\nreturn typeof(varaible);e\n}\ny\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\ndef showllTypes(varaible);\n\nreturn typeof(varaible);e\n}\ny\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\ndef showAllTypes(varaible);\n\nreturn typeof(varaible);e\n}\ny\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nde showAllTypes(varaible);\n\nreturn typeof(varaible);e\n}\ny\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nd showAllTypes(varaible);\n\nreturn typeof(varaible);e\n}\ny\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n showAllTypes(varaible);\n\nreturn typeof(varaible);e\n}\ny\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */ showAllTypes(varaible);\n\nreturn typeof(varaible);e\n}\ny\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n   showAllTypes(varaible);\n\nreturn typeof(varaible);e\n}\ny\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  showAllTypes(varaible);\n\nreturn typeof(varaible);e\n}\ny\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nshowAllTypes(varaible);\n\nreturn typeof(varaible);e\n}\ny\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n  n\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n  nm\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n  nma\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n  n\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n  na\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n  nam\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n  name\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n  name \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n  name =\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n  name = \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n  name = A\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n  name = An\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n  name = And\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n  name = Ande\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n  name = Ander\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n  name = Anders\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n  name = Anderso\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n  name = Ander\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n  name = Ande\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n  name = And\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n  name = An\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n  name = A\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n  name = \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n  name = a\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n  name = an\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n  name = and\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n  name = ande\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n  name = ander\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n  name = anders\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n  name = anderso\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n  name = anderson\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n  name = anderson\n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n  name = anderson\n  c\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n  name = anderson\n  ca\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n  name = anderson\n  cap\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n  name = anderson\n  c\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n  name = anderson\n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n  name = anderson\n  C\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n  name = anderson\n  CA\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n  name = anderson\n  CAP\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n  name = anderson\n  CAP \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n  name = anderson\n  CAP =\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n  name = anderson\n  CAP = \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n  name = anderson\n  CAP = n\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n  name = anderson\n  CAP = na\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n  name = anderson\n  CAP = nam\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n  name = anderson\n  CAP = name\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n  name = anderson\n  CAP = name.\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n  name = anderson\n  CAP = name.u\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n  name = anderson\n  CAP = name.uo\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n  name = anderson\n  CAP = name.uop\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n  name = anderson\n  CAP = name.u\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n  name = anderson\n  CAP = name.up\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n  name = anderson\n  CAP = name.upp\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n  name = anderson\n  CAP = name.uppe\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n  name = anderson\n  CAP = name.upper\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n  name = anderson\n  CAP = name.upper()\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n  name = anderson\n  CAP = name.upper();\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n  name = anderson\n  CAP = name.upper();\n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n  name = anderson\n  CAP = name.upper();\n  p\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n  name = anderson\n  CAP = name.upper();\n  pr\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n  name = anderson\n  CAP = name.upper();\n  pri\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n  name = anderson\n  CAP = name.upper();\n  prin\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n  name = anderson\n  CAP = name.upper();\n  print\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n  name = anderson\n  CAP = name.upper();\n  print()\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n  name = anderson\n  CAP = name.upper();\n  print(C)\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n  name = anderson\n  CAP = name.upper();\n  print(CA)\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n  name = anderson\n  CAP = name.upper();\n  print(CAP)\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n  name = anderson\n  CAP = name.upper();\n  print(CAP);\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() \n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\n}\n\nmodule.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function createLyrics(songData) {\n  // Use template literals to create lyrics from the songData object\n  // The songData object will have properties like artist, title, verse, chorus\n  // Return the formatted lyrics string\n}\n\nmodule.exports = createLyrics;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex5-template-lyrics.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function simulateBattle(player1, player2) {\n  /* take two player objects and simulate them attacking each other\n   return an object with the updated health of both players after one round\n  example:  */\n}\n\nmodule.exports = simulateBattle;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex8-battle-simulation.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const helloWorld = require('../../exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world');\n\ndescribe('hello world function', () => {\n  test('should log \"Hello World!\" to the console', () => {\n    const consoleSpy = jest.spyOn(console, 'log');\n    helloWorld();\n    expect(consoleSpy).toHaveBeenCalledWith('Hello World!');\n    consoleSpy.mockRestore();\n  });\n});\n","file":"tests/easy/ex1.test.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const showAllTypes = require('../../exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker');\n\ndescribe('Show All Types function', () => {\n  test('should return an object with all the types', () => {\n    const result = showAllTypes();\n    \n    expect(result).toHaveProperty('object');\n    expect(result).toHaveProperty('array');\n    expect(result).toHaveProperty('string');\n    expect(result).toHaveProperty('number');\n    expect(result).toHaveProperty('boolean');\n    expect(result).toHaveProperty('null');\n    expect(result).toHaveProperty('undefined');\n    expect(result).toHaveProperty('nan');\n    \n    expect(result.object).toBe('object');\n    expect(result.array).toBe('object');\n    expect(result.string).toBe('string');\n    expect(result.number).toBe('number');\n    expect(result.boolean).toBe('boolean');\n    expect(result.null).toBe('object');\n    expect(result.undefined).toBe('undefined');\n    expect(result.nan).toBe('number');\n  });\n});\n","file":"tests/easy/ex2.test.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const screamName = require('../../exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer');\n\ndescribe('Name Screamer function', () => {\n  test('should convert name to uppercase and add exclamation marks', () => {\n    expect(screamName('john')).toBe('JOHN!!!');\n    expect(screamName('Sarah')).toBe('SARAH!!!');\n    expect(screamName('bob smith')).toBe('BOB SMITH!!!');\n  });\n});\n","file":"tests/easy/ex6.test.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const checkResolution = require('../../exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker');\n\ndescribe('Resolution Checker function', () => {\n  test('should return \"landscape\" when width > height', () => {\n    expect(checkResolution(1920, 1080)).toBe('landscape');\n    expect(checkResolution(800, 600)).toBe('landscape');\n  });\n\n  test('should return \"portrait\" when height >= width', () => {\n    expect(checkResolution(1080, 1920)).toBe('portrait');\n    expect(checkResolution(500, 500)).toBe('portrait');\n  });\n});\n","file":"tests/medium/ex3.test.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const reverseString = require('../../exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string');\n\ndescribe('Reverse String function', () => {\n  test('should reverse a string', () => {\n    expect(reverseString('hello')).toBe('olleh');\n    expect(reverseString('JavaScript')).toBe('tpircSavaJ');\n    expect(reverseString('12345')).toBe('54321');\n  });\n\n  test('should handle empty string', () => );\n\n  test('should handle single character', () => );\n});\n","file":"tests/medium/ex9.test.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const rollDice = require('../../exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller');\n\ndescribe('Dice Roller function', () => {\n  test('should return a number between 1 and 6', () => {\n    // Run multiple tests to ensure randomness\n    for (let i = 0; i < 100; i++) {\n      const result = rollDice();\n      expect(result).toBeGreaterThanOrEqual(1);\n      expect(result).toBeLessThanOrEqual(6);\n      expect(Number.isInteger(result)).toBe(true);\n    }\n  });\n});\n","file":"tests/medium/ex4.test.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const createLyrics = require('../../exercises/hard/ex5-template-lyrics');\n\ndescribe('Template Literals Lyrics function', () => {\n  test('should create lyrics using template literals', () => {\n    const songData = {\n      artist: 'Test Artist',\n      title: 'Test Song',\n      verse: 'This is a test verse',\n      chorus: 'This is a test chorus'\n    };\n    \n    const result = createLyrics(songData);\n    \n    expect(result).toContain(songData.artist);\n    expect(result).toContain(songData.title);\n    expect(result).toContain(songData.verse);\n    expect(result).toContain(songData.chorus);\n    \n    const functionString = createLyrics.toString();\n    expect(functionString).toMatch(/`.*\\$.*`/s);\n  });\n});\n","file":"tests/hard/ex5.test.js","language":"javascript"}
= require('../../exercises/hard/ex7-player-class');\n\ndescribe('Player Class', () => {\n  test('should create a player with all required properties', () => {\n    const player = new Player('Hero', 100, 'Sword', 10, 25);\n    \n    expect(player.name).toBe('Hero');\n    expect(player.health).toBe(100);\n    expect(player.weapon).toBe('Sword');\n    expect(player.speed).toBe(10);\n    expect(player.damage).toBe(25);\n  });\n  \n  test('createPlayer function should return a Player instance', () => {\n    const player = createPlayer('Villain', 80, 'Axe', 8, 30);\n    \n    expect(player instanceof Player).toBe(true);\n    expect(player.name).toBe('Villain');\n    expect(player.health).toBe(80);\n    expect(player.weapon).toBe('Axe');\n    expect(player.speed).toBe(8);\n    expect(player.damage).toBe(30);\n  });\n});\n","file":"tests/hard/ex7.test.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const simulateBattle = require('../../exercises/hard/ex8-battle-simulation');\n\ndescribe('Battle Simulation function', () => {\n  test('should reduce health of both players based on damage', () => {\n    const player1 = ;\n    const player2 = ;\n    \n    const result = simulateBattle(player1, player2);\n    \n    expect(result).toHaveProperty('player1Health');\n    expect(result).toHaveProperty('player2Health');\n    expect(result.player1Health).toBe(85); // 100 - 15\n    expect(result.player2Health).toBe(60); // 80 - 20\n  });\n});\n","file":"tests/hard/ex8.test.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n}\n\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n}\n\ni\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n}\n\nif\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n}\n\nif \nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n}\n\nif l\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n}\n\nif ()\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n}\n\nif (\"\")\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n}\n\nif (\"l\")\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n}\n\nif (\"la\")\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n}\n\nif (\"lan\")\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n}\n\nif (\"land\")\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n}\n\nif (\"la\")\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n}\n\nif (\"l\")\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n}\n\nif (\"\")\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n}\n\nif (\")\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n}\n\nif (\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n}\n\nif module.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n}\n\nifmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n}\n\nimodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n}\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}