{"text":"6:33:24 PM [info] Activating VS Code Recorder\n","file":"extension-output-MattiaConsiglio.vs-code-recorder-#1-VS Code Recorder","language":"Log"}
{"text":"6:33:24 PM [info] Activating VS Code Recorder\n6:34:51 PM [info] Recording started\n","file":"extension-output-MattiaConsiglio.vs-code-recorder-#1-VS Code Recorder","language":"Log"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  print(\"Hello World!add\")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  print(\"Hello World!\")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nshowAllTypes(varaible);\n\nreturn typeof(varaible);\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n  name = anderson\n  CAP = name.upper();\n  print(CAP);\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n \n  CAP = name.upper();\n  print(CAP);\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n\n  CAP = name.upper();\n  print(CAP);\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n\n  CAP = name.upper();\n  print(CAP);\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n}\ni\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n}\nif\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n}\nif \nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n}\nif ()\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n}\nif\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n}\ni\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n  \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n\n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n\n  i\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n\n  if\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n\n  if \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n\n  if l\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n\n  if la\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n\n  if lan\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n\n  if l\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n\n  if \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n\n  if ()\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n\n  if (l)\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n\n  if (la)\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n\n  if (lan)\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n\n  if (land)\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n\n  if (lands)\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n\n  if (landsc)\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n\n  if (landso)\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n\n  if (landsoc)\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n\n  if (landsoca)\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n\n  if (landso)\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n\n  if (lands)\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n\n  if (land)\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n\n  if (lan)\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n\n  if (la)\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n\n  if (l)\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n\n  if ()\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n\n  if (w)\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n\n  if (wi)\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n\n  if (wid)\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n\n  if (widt)\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n\n  if (width)\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n\n  if (width )\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n\n  if (width >)\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n\n  if (width > )\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n\n  if (width > h)\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n\n  if (width > he)\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n\n  if (width > hei)\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n\n  if (width > heig)\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n\n  if (width > heigh)\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n\n  if (width > height)\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n\n  if (width > height)\n    \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n\n  if (width > height)\n    \n    \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n\n  if (width > height)\n    \n    \n    \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n\n  if (width > height)\n\n    \n    \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n\n  if (width > height)\n\n    r\n    \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n\n  if (width > height)\n\n    re\n    \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n\n  if (width > height)\n\n    ret\n    \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n\n  if (width > height)\n\n    retu\n    \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n\n  if (width > height)\n\n    retur\n    \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n\n  if (width > height)\n\n    return\n    \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n\n  if (width > height)\n\n    return \n    \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n\n  if (width > height)\n\n    return l\n    \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n\n  if (width > height)\n\n    return la\n    \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n\n  if (width > height)\n\n    return lan\n    \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n\n  if (width > height)\n\n    return land\n    \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n\n  if (width > height)\n\n    return lands\n    \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n\n  if (width > height)\n\n    return lan\n    \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n\n  if (width > height)\n\n    return la\n    \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n\n  if (width > height)\n\n    return l\n    \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n\n  if (width > height)\n\n    return \n    \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n\n  if (width > height)\n\n    return \"\"\n    \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n\n  if (width > height)\n\n    return \"l\"\n    \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n\n  if (width > height)\n\n    return \"la\"\n    \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n\n  if (width > height)\n\n    return \"lan\"\n    \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n\n  if (width > height)\n\n    return \"land\"\n    \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n\n  if (width > height)\n\n    return \"lands\"\n    \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n\n  if (width > height)\n\n    return \"landso\"\n    \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n\n  if (width > height)\n\n    return \"landsoc\"\n    \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n\n  if (width > height)\n\n    return \"lands\"\n    \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n\n  if (width > height)\n\n    return \"landsp\"\n    \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n\n  if (width > height)\n\n    return \"landspc\"\n    \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n\n  if (width > height)\n\n    return \"landspca\"\n    \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n\n  if (width > height)\n\n    return \"landsp\"\n    \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n\n  if (width > height)\n\n    return \"landspa\"\n    \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n\n  if (width > height)\n\n    return \"landspac\"\n    \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n\n  if (width > height)\n\n    return \"landspace\"\n    \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n\n  if (width > height)\n\n    return \"landspace\";\n    \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n\n  if (width > height)\n\n    return \"landsace\";\n    \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n\n  if (width > height)\n\n    return \"landscace\";\n    \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n\n  if (width > height)\n\n    return \"landscae\";\n    \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n\n  if (width > height)\n\n    return \"landscape\";\n    \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n\n  if (width > height)\n\n    return \"landscape\";\n    \n    \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n\n  if (width > height)\n\n    return \"landscape\";\n    \n    \n    \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n\n  if (width > height)\n\n    return \"landscape\";\n    \n    \n    \n    \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n\n  if (width > height)\n\n    return \"landscape\";\n\n    \n    \n    \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n\n  if (width > height)\n\n    return \"landscape\";\n\n    i\n    \n    \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n\n  if (width > height)\n\n    return \"landscape\";\n\n    if\n    \n    \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n\n  if (width > height)\n\n    return \"landscape\";\n\n    if \n    \n    \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n\n  if (width > height)\n\n    return \"landscape\";\n}\n    if \n    \n    \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n\n  if (width > height)\n\n    return \"landscape\";\n}\n   {} if \n    \n    \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n\n  if (width > height)\n\n    return \"landscape\";\n}\n    if\n    \n    \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n\n  if (width > height)\n\n    return \"landscape\";\n}\n    if    \n    \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n\n  if (width > height)\n\n    return \"landscape\";\n}\n    i    \n    \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n\n  if (width > height)\n\n    return \"landscape\";\n}\n        \n    \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n\n  if (width > height)\n\n    return \"landscape\";\n}\n   if (height >= )\n\n   }     \n    \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n\n  if (width > height)\n{}\n    return \"landscape\";\n}\n   if (height >= )\n\n   }     \n    \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n\n  if (width > height)\n\n   if (height >= )\n\n   }     \n    \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n\n  if (width > height)\n\n   if (height >= w)\n\n   }     \n    \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n\n  if (width > height)\n\n   if (height >= we)\n\n   }     \n    \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n\n  if (width > height)\n\n   if (height >= wei)\n\n   }     \n    \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n\n  if (width > height)\n\n   if (height >= weig)\n\n   }     \n    \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n\n  if (width > height)\n\n   if (height >= weigh)\n\n   }     \n    \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n\n  if (width > height)\n\n   if (height >= weight)\n\n   }     \n    \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n\n  if (width > height)\n\n   if (height >= weight)\n{}\n   }     \n    \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n\n  if (width > height)\n\n   if (height >= weight)\n     \n    \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n\n  if (width > height)\n\n   if (height >= weigt)\n     \n    \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n\n  if (width > height)\n\n   if (height >= weit)\n     \n    \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n\n  if (width > height)\n\n   if (height >= wet)\n     \n    \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n\n  if (width > height)\n\n   if (height >= wt)\n     \n    \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n\n  if (width > height)\n\n   if (height >= wit)\n     \n    \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n\n  if (width > height)\n\n   if (height >= widt)\n     \n    \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n\n  if (width > height)\n\n   if (height >= widtt)\n     \n    \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n\n  if (width > height)\n\n   if (height >= width)\n     \n    \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() \n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n  \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  M\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  Ma\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  Mat\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  Math\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  Math.\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  Math.r\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  Math.ra\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  Math.ran\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  Math.rand\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  Math.rando\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  Math.random\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  Math.random()\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  Math.random(M)\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  Math.random(Ma)\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  Math.random(Mat)\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  Math.random(Math)\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  Math.random(Ma)\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  Math.random(M)\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  Math.random()\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  Math.rando()\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  Math.rand()\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  Math.ran()\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  Math.ra()\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  Math.r()\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  Math.()\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  Math.4()\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  Math.f()\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  Math.fl()\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  Math.flo()\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  Math.floo()\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  Math.floor()\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  Math.floor(M)\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  Math.floor(Ma)\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  Math.floor(Mat)\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  Math.floor(Math)\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  Math.floor(Math.)\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  Math.floor(Math.r)\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  Math.floor(Math.ra)\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  Math.floor(Math.ran)\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  Math.floor(Math.rand)\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  Math.floor(Math.rando)\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  Math.floor(Math.random)\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  Math.floor(Math.random) \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  Math.floor(Math.random) ()\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  Math.floor(Math.random()) \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  Math.floor(Math.random( )) \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  Math.floor(Math.random()*) \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  Math.floor(Math.random()* ) \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  Math.floor(Math.random()* 6) \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  Math.floor(Math.random()* 7) \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  Math.floor(Math.random()* 7 ) \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  Math.floor(Math.random()* 7)\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  Math.floor(Math.random()* 7);\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\n}\n\nmodule.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\n\n}\n\nmodule.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\nr\n}\n\nmodule.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\nre\n}\n\nmodule.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\nret\n}\n\nmodule.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\nretu\n}\n\nmodule.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\nretur\n}\n\nmodule.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\nreturn\n}\n\nmodule.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\nreturn \n}\n\nmodule.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\nreturn s\n}\n\nmodule.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\nreturn st\n}\n\nmodule.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\nreturn str\n}\n\nmodule.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\nreturn str.\n}\n\nmodule.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\nreturn str.s\n}\n\nmodule.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\nreturn str.sp\n}\n\nmodule.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\nreturn str.spl\n}\n\nmodule.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\nreturn str.spli\n}\n\nmodule.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\nreturn str.spliy\n}\n\nmodule.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\nreturn str.split\n}\n\nmodule.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\nreturn str.split()\n}\n\nmodule.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\nreturn str.split(\"\")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\nreturn str.split(\"\".)\n}\n\nmodule.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\nreturn str.split(\"\".r)\n}\n\nmodule.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\nreturn str.split(\"\".re)\n}\n\nmodule.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\nreturn str.split(\"\".rev)\n}\n\nmodule.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\nreturn str.split(\"\".reve)\n}\n\nmodule.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\nreturn str.split(\"\".rever)\n}\n\nmodule.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\nreturn str.split(\"\".revers)\n}\n\nmodule.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\nreturn str.split(\"\".reverse)\n}\n\nmodule.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\nreturn str.split(\"\".reverse())\n}\n\nmodule.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\nreturn str.split(\"\").reverse)\n}\n\nmodule.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\nreturn str.split(\"\").reverse\n}\n\nmodule.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\nreturn str.split(\").reverse\n}\n\nmodule.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\nreturn str.split().reverse\n}\n\nmodule.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\nreturn str.split('').reverse\n}\n\nmodule.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\nreturn str.split(' ').reverse\n}\n\nmodule.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\nreturn str.split(' ').reverse()\n}\n\nmodule.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\nreturn str.split(' ').reverse().\n}\n\nmodule.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\nreturn str.split(' ').reverse().j\n}\n\nmodule.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\nreturn str.split(' ').reverse().jo\n}\n\nmodule.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\nreturn str.split(' ').reverse().joi\n}\n\nmodule.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\nreturn str.split(' ').reverse().join\n}\n\nmodule.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\nreturn str.split(' ').reverse().join()\n}\n\nmodule.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\nreturn str.split(' ').reverse().join('')\n}\n\nmodule.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\nreturn str.split(' ').reverse().join('';)\n}\n\nmodule.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\nreturn str.split(' ').reverse().join('');\n}\n\nmodule.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function createLyrics(songData) {\n  // Use template literals to create lyrics from the songData object\n  // The songData object will have properties like artist, title, verse, chorus\n  // Return the formatted lyrics string\n}\n\nmodule.exports = createLyrics;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex5-template-lyrics.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function createLyrics(songData) {\n  // Use template literals to create lyrics from the songData object\n  // The songData object will have properties like artist, title, verse, chorus\n  // Return the formatted lyrics string\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = createLyrics;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex5-template-lyrics.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function createLyrics(songData) {\n  // Use template literals to create lyrics from the songData object\n  // The songData object will have properties like artist, title, verse, chorus\n  // Return the formatted lyrics string\n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = createLyrics;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex5-template-lyrics.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function createLyrics(songData) {\n  // Use template literals to create lyrics from the songData object\n  // The songData object will have properties like artist, title, verse, chorus\n  // Return the formatted lyrics string\n  \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = createLyrics;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex5-template-lyrics.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function createLyrics(songData) {\n  // Use template literals to create lyrics from the songData object\n  // The songData object will have properties like artist, title, verse, chorus\n  // Return the formatted lyrics string\n\n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = createLyrics;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex5-template-lyrics.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function createLyrics(songData) {\n  // Use template literals to create lyrics from the songData object\n  // The songData object will have properties like artist, title, verse, chorus\n  // Return the formatted lyrics string\n\n  r\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = createLyrics;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex5-template-lyrics.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function createLyrics(songData) {\n  // Use template literals to create lyrics from the songData object\n  // The songData object will have properties like artist, title, verse, chorus\n  // Return the formatted lyrics string\n\n  re\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = createLyrics;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex5-template-lyrics.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function createLyrics(songData) {\n  // Use template literals to create lyrics from the songData object\n  // The songData object will have properties like artist, title, verse, chorus\n  // Return the formatted lyrics string\n\n  ret\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = createLyrics;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex5-template-lyrics.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function createLyrics(songData) {\n  // Use template literals to create lyrics from the songData object\n  // The songData object will have properties like artist, title, verse, chorus\n  // Return the formatted lyrics string\n\n  retu\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = createLyrics;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex5-template-lyrics.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function createLyrics(songData) {\n  // Use template literals to create lyrics from the songData object\n  // The songData object will have properties like artist, title, verse, chorus\n  // Return the formatted lyrics string\n\n  retur\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = createLyrics;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex5-template-lyrics.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function createLyrics(songData) {\n  // Use template literals to create lyrics from the songData object\n  // The songData object will have properties like artist, title, verse, chorus\n  // Return the formatted lyrics string\n\n  return\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = createLyrics;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex5-template-lyrics.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function createLyrics(songData) {\n  // Use template literals to create lyrics from the songData object\n  // The songData object will have properties like artist, title, verse, chorus\n  // Return the formatted lyrics string\n\n  return \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = createLyrics;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex5-template-lyrics.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function createLyrics(songData) {\n  // Use template literals to create lyrics from the songData object\n  // The songData object will have properties like artist, title, verse, chorus\n  // Return the formatted lyrics string\n\n  return ()\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = createLyrics;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex5-template-lyrics.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function createLyrics(songData) {\n  // Use template literals to create lyrics from the songData object\n  // The songData object will have properties like artist, title, verse, chorus\n  // Return the formatted lyrics string\n\n  return (s)\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = createLyrics;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex5-template-lyrics.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function createLyrics(songData) {\n  // Use template literals to create lyrics from the songData object\n  // The songData object will have properties like artist, title, verse, chorus\n  // Return the formatted lyrics string\n\n  return (st)\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = createLyrics;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex5-template-lyrics.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function createLyrics(songData) {\n  // Use template literals to create lyrics from the songData object\n  // The songData object will have properties like artist, title, verse, chorus\n  // Return the formatted lyrics string\n\n  return (str)\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = createLyrics;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex5-template-lyrics.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function createLyrics(songData) {\n  // Use template literals to create lyrics from the songData object\n  // The songData object will have properties like artist, title, verse, chorus\n  // Return the formatted lyrics string\n\n  return (stri)\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = createLyrics;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex5-template-lyrics.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function createLyrics(songData) {\n  // Use template literals to create lyrics from the songData object\n  // The songData object will have properties like artist, title, verse, chorus\n  // Return the formatted lyrics string\n\n  return (strin)\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = createLyrics;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex5-template-lyrics.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function createLyrics(songData) {\n  // Use template literals to create lyrics from the songData object\n  // The songData object will have properties like artist, title, verse, chorus\n  // Return the formatted lyrics string\n\n  return (string)\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = createLyrics;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex5-template-lyrics.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function createLyrics(songData) {\n  // Use template literals to create lyrics from the songData object\n  // The songData object will have properties like artist, title, verse, chorus\n  // Return the formatted lyrics string\n\n  return (string\\)\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = createLyrics;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex5-template-lyrics.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function createLyrics(songData) {\n  // Use template literals to create lyrics from the songData object\n  // The songData object will have properties like artist, title, verse, chorus\n  // Return the formatted lyrics string\n\n  return (strin)\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = createLyrics;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex5-template-lyrics.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function createLyrics(songData) {\n  // Use template literals to create lyrics from the songData object\n  // The songData object will have properties like artist, title, verse, chorus\n  // Return the formatted lyrics string\n\n  return (stri)\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = createLyrics;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex5-template-lyrics.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function createLyrics(songData) {\n  // Use template literals to create lyrics from the songData object\n  // The songData object will have properties like artist, title, verse, chorus\n  // Return the formatted lyrics string\n\n  return (str)\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = createLyrics;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex5-template-lyrics.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function createLyrics(songData) {\n  // Use template literals to create lyrics from the songData object\n  // The songData object will have properties like artist, title, verse, chorus\n  // Return the formatted lyrics string\n\n  return (st)\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = createLyrics;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex5-template-lyrics.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function createLyrics(songData) {\n  // Use template literals to create lyrics from the songData object\n  // The songData object will have properties like artist, title, verse, chorus\n  // Return the formatted lyrics string\n\n  return (s)\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = createLyrics;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex5-template-lyrics.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function createLyrics(songData) {\n  // Use template literals to create lyrics from the songData object\n  // The songData object will have properties like artist, title, verse, chorus\n  // Return the formatted lyrics string\n\n  return ()\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = createLyrics;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex5-template-lyrics.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function createLyrics(songData) {\n  // Use template literals to create lyrics from the songData object\n  // The songData object will have properties like artist, title, verse, chorus\n  // Return the formatted lyrics string\n\n  return (\"\")\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = createLyrics;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex5-template-lyrics.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function createLyrics(songData) {\n  // Use template literals to create lyrics from the songData object\n  // The songData object will have properties like artist, title, verse, chorus\n  // Return the formatted lyrics string\n\n  return \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = createLyrics;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex5-template-lyrics.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function createLyrics(songData) {\n  // Use template literals to create lyrics from the songData object\n  // The songData object will have properties like artist, title, verse, chorus\n  // Return the formatted lyrics string\n\n  return ''\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = createLyrics;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex5-template-lyrics.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function createLyrics(songData) {\n  // Use template literals to create lyrics from the songData object\n  // The songData object will have properties like artist, title, verse, chorus\n  // Return the formatted lyrics string\n\n  return ``\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = createLyrics;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex5-template-lyrics.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function createLyrics(songData) {\n  // Use template literals to create lyrics from the songData object\n  // The songData object will have properties like artist, title, verse, chorus\n  // Return the formatted lyrics string\n\n  return `\"`\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = createLyrics;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex5-template-lyrics.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function createLyrics(songData) {\n  // Use template literals to create lyrics from the songData object\n  // The songData object will have properties like artist, title, verse, chorus\n  // Return the formatted lyrics string\n\n  return `M`\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = createLyrics;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex5-template-lyrics.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function createLyrics(songData) {\n  // Use template literals to create lyrics from the songData object\n  // The songData object will have properties like artist, title, verse, chorus\n  // Return the formatted lyrics string\n\n  return `MY`\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = createLyrics;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex5-template-lyrics.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function createLyrics(songData) {\n  // Use template literals to create lyrics from the songData object\n  // The songData object will have properties like artist, title, verse, chorus\n  // Return the formatted lyrics string\n\n  return `MY=`\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = createLyrics;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex5-template-lyrics.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function createLyrics(songData) {\n  // Use template literals to create lyrics from the songData object\n  // The songData object will have properties like artist, title, verse, chorus\n  // Return the formatted lyrics string\n\n  return `M`\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = createLyrics;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex5-template-lyrics.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function createLyrics(songData) {\n  // Use template literals to create lyrics from the songData object\n  // The songData object will have properties like artist, title, verse, chorus\n  // Return the formatted lyrics string\n\n  return `My`\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = createLyrics;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex5-template-lyrics.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function createLyrics(songData) {\n  // Use template literals to create lyrics from the songData object\n  // The songData object will have properties like artist, title, verse, chorus\n  // Return the formatted lyrics string\n\n  return `My `\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = createLyrics;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex5-template-lyrics.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function createLyrics(songData) {\n  // Use template literals to create lyrics from the songData object\n  // The songData object will have properties like artist, title, verse, chorus\n  // Return the formatted lyrics string\n\n  return `M`\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = createLyrics;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex5-template-lyrics.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function createLyrics(songData) {\n  // Use template literals to create lyrics from the songData object\n  // The songData object will have properties like artist, title, verse, chorus\n  // Return the formatted lyrics string\n\n  return ``\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = createLyrics;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex5-template-lyrics.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function createLyrics(songData) {\n  // Use template literals to create lyrics from the songData object\n  // The songData object will have properties like artist, title, verse, chorus\n  // Return the formatted lyrics string\n\n  return `J`\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = createLyrics;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex5-template-lyrics.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function createLyrics(songData) {\n  // Use template literals to create lyrics from the songData object\n  // The songData object will have properties like artist, title, verse, chorus\n  // Return the formatted lyrics string\n\n  return `Jo`\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = createLyrics;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex5-template-lyrics.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function createLyrics(songData) {\n  // Use template literals to create lyrics from the songData object\n  // The songData object will have properties like artist, title, verse, chorus\n  // Return the formatted lyrics string\n\n  return `Joh`\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = createLyrics;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex5-template-lyrics.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function createLyrics(songData) {\n  // Use template literals to create lyrics from the songData object\n  // The songData object will have properties like artist, title, verse, chorus\n  // Return the formatted lyrics string\n\n  return `J`\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = createLyrics;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex5-template-lyrics.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function createLyrics(songData) {\n  // Use template literals to create lyrics from the songData object\n  // The songData object will have properties like artist, title, verse, chorus\n  // Return the formatted lyrics string\n\n  return ``\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = createLyrics;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex5-template-lyrics.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function createLyrics(songData) {\n  // Use template literals to create lyrics from the songData object\n  // The songData object will have properties like artist, title, verse, chorus\n  // Return the formatted lyrics string\n\n  return `s`\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = createLyrics;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex5-template-lyrics.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function createLyrics(songData) {\n  // Use template literals to create lyrics from the songData object\n  // The songData object will have properties like artist, title, verse, chorus\n  // Return the formatted lyrics string\n\n  return `so`\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = createLyrics;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex5-template-lyrics.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function createLyrics(songData) {\n  // Use template literals to create lyrics from the songData object\n  // The songData object will have properties like artist, title, verse, chorus\n  // Return the formatted lyrics string\n\n  return `son`\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = createLyrics;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex5-template-lyrics.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function createLyrics(songData) {\n  // Use template literals to create lyrics from the songData object\n  // The songData object will have properties like artist, title, verse, chorus\n  // Return the formatted lyrics string\n\n  return `song`\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = createLyrics;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex5-template-lyrics.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function createLyrics(songData) {\n  // Use template literals to create lyrics from the songData object\n  // The songData object will have properties like artist, title, verse, chorus\n  // Return the formatted lyrics string\n\n  return `so`\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = createLyrics;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex5-template-lyrics.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function createLyrics(songData) {\n  // Use template literals to create lyrics from the songData object\n  // The songData object will have properties like artist, title, verse, chorus\n  // Return the formatted lyrics string\n\n  return `s`\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = createLyrics;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex5-template-lyrics.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function createLyrics(songData) {\n  // Use template literals to create lyrics from the songData object\n  // The songData object will have properties like artist, title, verse, chorus\n  // Return the formatted lyrics string\n\n  return ``\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = createLyrics;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex5-template-lyrics.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function createLyrics(songData) {\n  // Use template literals to create lyrics from the songData object\n  // The songData object will have properties like artist, title, verse, chorus\n  // Return the formatted lyrics string\n\n  return `$`\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = createLyrics;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex5-template-lyrics.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function createLyrics(songData) {\n  // Use template literals to create lyrics from the songData object\n  // The songData object will have properties like artist, title, verse, chorus\n  // Return the formatted lyrics string\n\n  return `$[]`\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = createLyrics;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex5-template-lyrics.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function createLyrics(songData) {\n  // Use template literals to create lyrics from the songData object\n  // The songData object will have properties like artist, title, verse, chorus\n  // Return the formatted lyrics string\n\n  return `${}`\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = createLyrics;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex5-template-lyrics.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function createLyrics(songData) {\n  // Use template literals to create lyrics from the songData object\n  // The songData object will have properties like artist, title, verse, chorus\n  // Return the formatted lyrics string\n\n  return `$`\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = createLyrics;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex5-template-lyrics.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function createLyrics(songData) {\n  // Use template literals to create lyrics from the songData object\n  // The songData object will have properties like artist, title, verse, chorus\n  // Return the formatted lyrics string\n\n  return `$ `\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = createLyrics;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex5-template-lyrics.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function createLyrics(songData) {\n  // Use template literals to create lyrics from the songData object\n  // The songData object will have properties like artist, title, verse, chorus\n  // Return the formatted lyrics string\n\n  return `$ b`\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = createLyrics;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex5-template-lyrics.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function createLyrics(songData) {\n  // Use template literals to create lyrics from the songData object\n  // The songData object will have properties like artist, title, verse, chorus\n  // Return the formatted lyrics string\n\n  return `$ by`\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = createLyrics;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex5-template-lyrics.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function createLyrics(songData) {\n  // Use template literals to create lyrics from the songData object\n  // The songData object will have properties like artist, title, verse, chorus\n  // Return the formatted lyrics string\n\n  return `$ by `\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = createLyrics;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex5-template-lyrics.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function createLyrics(songData) {\n  // Use template literals to create lyrics from the songData object\n  // The songData object will have properties like artist, title, verse, chorus\n  // Return the formatted lyrics string\n\n  return `$ by R`\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = createLyrics;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex5-template-lyrics.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function createLyrics(songData) {\n  // Use template literals to create lyrics from the songData object\n  // The songData object will have properties like artist, title, verse, chorus\n  // Return the formatted lyrics string\n\n  return `$ by `\n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = createLyrics;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex5-template-lyrics.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function createLyrics(songData) {\n  // Use template literals to create lyrics from the songData object\n  // The songData object will have properties like artist, title, verse, chorus\n  // Return the formatted lyrics string\n\n  return `$ by `\n  r\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = createLyrics;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex5-template-lyrics.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function createLyrics(songData) {\n  // Use template literals to create lyrics from the songData object\n  // The songData object will have properties like artist, title, verse, chorus\n  // Return the formatted lyrics string\n\n  return `$ by `\n  re\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = createLyrics;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex5-template-lyrics.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function createLyrics(songData) {\n  // Use template literals to create lyrics from the songData object\n  // The songData object will have properties like artist, title, verse, chorus\n  // Return the formatted lyrics string\n\n  return `$ by `\n  ret\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = createLyrics;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex5-template-lyrics.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function createLyrics(songData) {\n  // Use template literals to create lyrics from the songData object\n  // The songData object will have properties like artist, title, verse, chorus\n  // Return the formatted lyrics string\n\n  return `$ by `\n  retu\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = createLyrics;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex5-template-lyrics.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function createLyrics(songData) {\n  // Use template literals to create lyrics from the songData object\n  // The songData object will have properties like artist, title, verse, chorus\n  // Return the formatted lyrics string\n\n  return `$ by `\n  retur\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = createLyrics;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex5-template-lyrics.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function createLyrics(songData) {\n  // Use template literals to create lyrics from the songData object\n  // The songData object will have properties like artist, title, verse, chorus\n  // Return the formatted lyrics string\n\n  return `$ by `\n  return\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = createLyrics;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex5-template-lyrics.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function createLyrics(songData) {\n  // Use template literals to create lyrics from the songData object\n  // The songData object will have properties like artist, title, verse, chorus\n  // Return the formatted lyrics string\n\n  return `$ by `\n  return \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = createLyrics;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex5-template-lyrics.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function createLyrics(songData) {\n  // Use template literals to create lyrics from the songData object\n  // The songData object will have properties like artist, title, verse, chorus\n  // Return the formatted lyrics string\n\n  return `$ by `\n  return \\\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = createLyrics;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex5-template-lyrics.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function createLyrics(songData) {\n  // Use template literals to create lyrics from the songData object\n  // The songData object will have properties like artist, title, verse, chorus\n  // Return the formatted lyrics string\n\n  return `$ by `\n  return\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = createLyrics;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex5-template-lyrics.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function createLyrics(songData) {\n  // Use template literals to create lyrics from the songData object\n  // The songData object will have properties like artist, title, verse, chorus\n  // Return the formatted lyrics string\n\n  return `$ by `\n  retur\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = createLyrics;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex5-template-lyrics.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function createLyrics(songData) {\n  // Use template literals to create lyrics from the songData object\n  // The songData object will have properties like artist, title, verse, chorus\n  // Return the formatted lyrics string\n\n  return `$ by `\n  retu\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = createLyrics;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex5-template-lyrics.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function createLyrics(songData) {\n  // Use template literals to create lyrics from the songData object\n  // The songData object will have properties like artist, title, verse, chorus\n  // Return the formatted lyrics string\n\n  return `$ by `\n  ret\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = createLyrics;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex5-template-lyrics.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function createLyrics(songData) {\n  // Use template literals to create lyrics from the songData object\n  // The songData object will have properties like artist, title, verse, chorus\n  // Return the formatted lyrics string\n\n  return `$ by `\n  re\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = createLyrics;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex5-template-lyrics.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function createLyrics(songData) {\n  // Use template literals to create lyrics from the songData object\n  // The songData object will have properties like artist, title, verse, chorus\n  // Return the formatted lyrics string\n\n  return `$ by `\n  r\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = createLyrics;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex5-template-lyrics.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function createLyrics(songData) {\n  // Use template literals to create lyrics from the songData object\n  // The songData object will have properties like artist, title, verse, chorus\n  // Return the formatted lyrics string\n\n  return `$ by `\n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = createLyrics;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex5-template-lyrics.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function createLyrics(songData) {\n  // Use template literals to create lyrics from the songData object\n  // The songData object will have properties like artist, title, verse, chorus\n  // Return the formatted lyrics string\n\n  return `$ by $`\n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = createLyrics;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex5-template-lyrics.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function createLyrics(songData) {\n  // Use template literals to create lyrics from the songData object\n  // The songData object will have properties like artist, title, verse, chorus\n  // Return the formatted lyrics string\n\n  return `$ by ${}`\n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = createLyrics;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex5-template-lyrics.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function createLyrics(songData) {\n  // Use template literals to create lyrics from the songData object\n  // The songData object will have properties like artist, title, verse, chorus\n  // Return the formatted lyrics string\n\n  return `$ by $ `\n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = createLyrics;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex5-template-lyrics.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function createLyrics(songData) {\n  // Use template literals to create lyrics from the songData object\n  // The songData object will have properties like artist, title, verse, chorus\n  // Return the formatted lyrics string\n\n  return `$ by $ $`\n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = createLyrics;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex5-template-lyrics.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function createLyrics(songData) {\n  // Use template literals to create lyrics from the songData object\n  // The songData object will have properties like artist, title, verse, chorus\n  // Return the formatted lyrics string\n\n  return `$ by $ ${}`\n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = createLyrics;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex5-template-lyrics.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function createLyrics(songData) {\n  // Use template literals to create lyrics from the songData object\n  // The songData object will have properties like artist, title, verse, chorus\n  // Return the formatted lyrics string\n\n  return `$ by $ $ `\n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = createLyrics;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex5-template-lyrics.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function createLyrics(songData) {\n  // Use template literals to create lyrics from the songData object\n  // The songData object will have properties like artist, title, verse, chorus\n  // Return the formatted lyrics string\n\n  return `$ by $ $ $`\n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = createLyrics;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex5-template-lyrics.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function createLyrics(songData) {\n  // Use template literals to create lyrics from the songData object\n  // The songData object will have properties like artist, title, verse, chorus\n  // Return the formatted lyrics string\n\n  return `$ by $ $ ${}`\n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = createLyrics;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex5-template-lyrics.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function createLyrics(songData) {\n  // Use template literals to create lyrics from the songData object\n  // The songData object will have properties like artist, title, verse, chorus\n  // Return the formatted lyrics string\n\n  return `$ by $ $ $`;\n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = createLyrics;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex5-template-lyrics.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function createLyrics(songData) {\n  // Use template literals to create lyrics from the songData object\n  // The songData object will have properties like artist, title, verse, chorus\n  // Return the formatted lyrics string\n\n  return `$ by\n   $ $ $`;\n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = createLyrics;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex5-template-lyrics.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function createLyrics(songData) {\n  // Use template literals to create lyrics from the songData object\n  // The songData object will have properties like artist, title, verse, chorus\n  // Return the formatted lyrics string\n\n  return `$ by\n $ $ $`;\n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = createLyrics;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex5-template-lyrics.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function createLyrics(songData) {\n  // Use template literals to create lyrics from the songData object\n  // The songData object will have properties like artist, title, verse, chorus\n  // Return the formatted lyrics string\n\n  return `$ by $ $ $`;\n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = createLyrics;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex5-template-lyrics.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function createLyrics(songData) {\n  // Use template literals to create lyrics from the songData object\n  // The songData object will have properties like artist, title, verse, chorus\n  // Return the formatted lyrics string\n\n  return `$ by $ \n  $ $`;\n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = createLyrics;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex5-template-lyrics.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function createLyrics(songData) {\n  // Use template literals to create lyrics from the songData object\n  // The songData object will have properties like artist, title, verse, chorus\n  // Return the formatted lyrics string\n\n  return `$ by $ \n  $ \n  $`;\n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = createLyrics;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex5-template-lyrics.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\nc\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\ncl\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\ncla\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\nclas\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\nclass\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\nclass \nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\nclas\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\ncla\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\ncl\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\nc\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n  \n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n  \n  \n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  \n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  c\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  co\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  con\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  cons\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  const\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constr\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constru\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  construc\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  construct\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructo\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor \n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor()\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(h)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(he)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(hea)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(heal)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(healy)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(healyy)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(healyty)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(healythy)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(healyy)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(healy)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(healty)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(healthy)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(healthy;)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(healthy )\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(healthy {})\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(healthy \n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health,y \n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, y \n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, wy \n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, wey \n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weay \n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapy \n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapoy \n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapony \n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon,y \n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, y \n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, sy \n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, spy \n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, sppy \n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, spey \n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speey \n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speedy \n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed,y \n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, y \n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, ny \n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, nay \n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, namy \n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, namey \n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name,y \n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, y \n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, dy \n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, day \n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damy \n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damay \n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagy \n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damaggy \n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damaghgy \n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy \n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.health = health;\n    this.health = health;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.health = health;\n    this.health = health;\n    \n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.health = health;\n    this.health = health;\n    this.health = health;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.health = health;\n    this.health = health;\n    this.health = health;\n    \n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.health = health;\n    this.health = health;\n    this.health = health;\n    this.health = health;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.healt = health;\n    this.health = health;\n    this.health = health;\n    this.health = health;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.heal = health;\n    this.health = health;\n    this.health = health;\n    this.health = health;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.hea = health;\n    this.health = health;\n    this.health = health;\n    this.health = health;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.he = health;\n    this.health = health;\n    this.health = health;\n    this.health = health;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.h = health;\n    this.health = health;\n    this.health = health;\n    this.health = health;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this. = health;\n    this.health = health;\n    this.health = health;\n    this.health = health;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.w = health;\n    this.health = health;\n    this.health = health;\n    this.health = health;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.we = health;\n    this.health = health;\n    this.health = health;\n    this.health = health;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.wea = health;\n    this.health = health;\n    this.health = health;\n    this.health = health;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weap = health;\n    this.health = health;\n    this.health = health;\n    this.health = health;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapo = health;\n    this.health = health;\n    this.health = health;\n    this.health = health;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = health;\n    this.health = health;\n    this.health = health;\n    this.health = health;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = healt;\n    this.health = health;\n    this.health = health;\n    this.health = health;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = heal;\n    this.health = health;\n    this.health = health;\n    this.health = health;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = hea;\n    this.health = health;\n    this.health = health;\n    this.health = health;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = he;\n    this.health = health;\n    this.health = health;\n    this.health = health;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = h;\n    this.health = health;\n    this.health = health;\n    this.health = health;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = ;\n    this.health = health;\n    this.health = health;\n    this.health = health;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = w;\n    this.health = health;\n    this.health = health;\n    this.health = health;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = we;\n    this.health = health;\n    this.health = health;\n    this.health = health;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = wea;\n    this.health = health;\n    this.health = health;\n    this.health = health;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weap;\n    this.health = health;\n    this.health = health;\n    this.health = health;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapo;\n    this.health = health;\n    this.health = health;\n    this.health = health;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.health = health;\n    this.health = health;\n    this.health = health;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.health = healt;\n    this.health = health;\n    this.health = health;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.health = heal;\n    this.health = health;\n    this.health = health;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.health = hea;\n    this.health = health;\n    this.health = health;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.health = he;\n    this.health = health;\n    this.health = health;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.health = h;\n    this.health = health;\n    this.health = health;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.health = ;\n    this.health = health;\n    this.health = health;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.health = w;\n    this.health = health;\n    this.health = health;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.health = we;\n    this.health = health;\n    this.health = health;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.health = wea;\n    this.health = health;\n    this.health = health;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.health = weap;\n    this.health = health;\n    this.health = health;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.health = weapo;\n    this.health = health;\n    this.health = health;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.health = weapon;\n    this.health = health;\n    this.health = health;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.healt = weapon;\n    this.health = health;\n    this.health = health;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.heal = weapon;\n    this.health = health;\n    this.health = health;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.hea = weapon;\n    this.health = health;\n    this.health = health;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.he = weapon;\n    this.health = health;\n    this.health = health;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.h = weapon;\n    this.health = health;\n    this.health = health;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this. = weapon;\n    this.health = health;\n    this.health = health;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.w = weapon;\n    this.health = health;\n    this.health = health;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.we = weapon;\n    this.health = health;\n    this.health = health;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.wea = weapon;\n    this.health = health;\n    this.health = health;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.weap = weapon;\n    this.health = health;\n    this.health = health;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.weapo = weapon;\n    this.health = health;\n    this.health = health;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.health = health;\n    this.health = health;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.weap = weapon;\n    this.health = health;\n    this.health = health;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.wea = weapon;\n    this.health = health;\n    this.health = health;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.we = weapon;\n    this.health = health;\n    this.health = health;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.w = weapon;\n    this.health = health;\n    this.health = health;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this. = weapon;\n    this.health = health;\n    this.health = health;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.s = weapon;\n    this.health = health;\n    this.health = health;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.so = weapon;\n    this.health = health;\n    this.health = health;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.soe = weapon;\n    this.health = health;\n    this.health = health;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.s = weapon;\n    this.health = health;\n    this.health = health;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.sp = weapon;\n    this.health = health;\n    this.health = health;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.spe = weapon;\n    this.health = health;\n    this.health = health;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.spee = weapon;\n    this.health = health;\n    this.health = health;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.speed = weapon;\n    this.health = health;\n    this.health = health;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.speed = weapo;\n    this.health = health;\n    this.health = health;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.speed = weap;\n    this.health = health;\n    this.health = health;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.speed = wea;\n    this.health = health;\n    this.health = health;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.speed = we;\n    this.health = health;\n    this.health = health;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.speed = w;\n    this.health = health;\n    this.health = health;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.speed = ;\n    this.health = health;\n    this.health = health;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.speed = s;\n    this.health = health;\n    this.health = health;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.speed = so;\n    this.health = health;\n    this.health = health;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.speed = soe;\n    this.health = health;\n    this.health = health;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.speed = soee;\n    this.health = health;\n    this.health = health;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.speed = so;\n    this.health = health;\n    this.health = health;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.speed = s;\n    this.health = health;\n    this.health = health;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.speed = sp;\n    this.health = health;\n    this.health = health;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.speed = spe;\n    this.health = health;\n    this.health = health;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.speed = spee;\n    this.health = health;\n    this.health = health;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.speed = speed;\n    this.health = health;\n    this.health = health;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.speed = speed;\n    this.health = healt;\n    this.health = health;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.speed = speed;\n    this.health = heal;\n    this.health = health;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.speed = speed;\n    this.health = hea;\n    this.health = health;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.speed = speed;\n    this.health = he;\n    this.health = health;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.speed = speed;\n    this.health = h;\n    this.health = health;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.speed = speed;\n    this.health = ;\n    this.health = health;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.speed = speed;\n    this.health = n;\n    this.health = health;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.speed = speed;\n    this.health = na;\n    this.health = health;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.speed = speed;\n    this.health = nam;\n    this.health = health;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.speed = speed;\n    this.health = name;\n    this.health = health;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.speed = speed;\n    this.healt = name;\n    this.health = health;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.speed = speed;\n    this.heal = name;\n    this.health = health;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.speed = speed;\n    this.hea = name;\n    this.health = health;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.speed = speed;\n    this.he = name;\n    this.health = health;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.speed = speed;\n    this.h = name;\n    this.health = health;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.speed = speed;\n    this. = name;\n    this.health = health;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.speed = speed;\n    this.n = name;\n    this.health = health;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.speed = speed;\n    this.na = name;\n    this.health = health;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.speed = speed;\n    this.nam = name;\n    this.health = health;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.speed = speed;\n    this.name = name;\n    this.health = health;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.speed = speed;\n    this.name = name;\n    this.healt = health;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.speed = speed;\n    this.name = name;\n    this.heal = health;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.speed = speed;\n    this.name = name;\n    this.hea = health;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.speed = speed;\n    this.name = name;\n    this.he = health;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.speed = speed;\n    this.name = name;\n    this.h = health;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.speed = speed;\n    this.name = name;\n    this. = health;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.speed = speed;\n    this.name = name;\n    this.d = health;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.speed = speed;\n    this.name = name;\n    this.da = health;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.speed = speed;\n    this.name = name;\n    this.dam = health;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.speed = speed;\n    this.name = name;\n    this.dama = health;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.speed = speed;\n    this.name = name;\n    this.damag = health;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.speed = speed;\n    this.name = name;\n    this.damage = health;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.speed = speed;\n    this.name = name;\n    this.damage = healt;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.speed = speed;\n    this.name = name;\n    this.damage = heal;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.speed = speed;\n    this.name = name;\n    this.damage = hea;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.speed = speed;\n    this.name = name;\n    this.damage = he;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.speed = speed;\n    this.name = name;\n    this.damage = h;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.speed = speed;\n    this.name = name;\n    this.damage = ;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.speed = speed;\n    this.name = name;\n    this.damage = d;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.speed = speed;\n    this.name = name;\n    this.damage = da;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.speed = speed;\n    this.name = name;\n    this.damage = dam;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.speed = speed;\n    this.name = name;\n    this.damage = dama;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.speed = speed;\n    this.name = name;\n    this.damage = damag;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.speed = speed;\n    this.name = name;\n    this.damage = damage;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.speed = speed;\n    this.name = name;\n    this.damage = damage;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) {\n  // Create and return a new Player object with the given propertie\n  returs\n}\n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.speed = speed;\n    this.name = name;\n    this.damage = damage;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) {\n  // Create and return a new Player object with the given propertie\n  returns\n}\n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.speed = speed;\n    this.name = name;\n    this.damage = damage;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) {\n  // Create and return a new Player object with the given propertie\n  return s\n}\n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.speed = speed;\n    this.name = name;\n    this.damage = damage;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) {\n  // Create and return a new Player object with the given propertie\n  returs\n}\n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.speed = speed;\n    this.name = name;\n    this.damage = damage;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.speed = speed;\n    this.name = name;\n    this.damage = damage;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) {\n  // Create and return a new Player object with the given propertie\n  returns\n}\n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.speed = speed;\n    this.name = name;\n    this.damage = damage;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) {\n  // Create and return a new Player object with the given propertie\n  return s\n}\n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.speed = speed;\n    this.name = name;\n    this.damage = damage;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) {\n  // Create and return a new Player object with the given propertie\n  return ``s\n}\n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.speed = speed;\n    this.name = name;\n    this.damage = damage;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) {\n  // Create and return a new Player object with the given propertie\n  return `=`s\n}\n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.speed = speed;\n    this.name = name;\n    this.damage = damage;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) {\n  // Create and return a new Player object with the given propertie\n  return s\n}\n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.speed = speed;\n    this.name = name;\n    this.damage = damage;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) {\n  // Create and return a new Player object with the given propertie\n  return ns\n}\n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.speed = speed;\n    this.name = name;\n    this.damage = damage;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) {\n  // Create and return a new Player object with the given propertie\n  return nes\n}\n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.speed = speed;\n    this.name = name;\n    this.damage = damage;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) {\n  // Create and return a new Player object with the given propertie\n  return news\n}\n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.speed = speed;\n    this.name = name;\n    this.damage = damage;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) {\n  // Create and return a new Player object with the given propertie\n  return new s\n}\n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.speed = speed;\n    this.name = name;\n    this.damage = damage;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) {\n  // Create and return a new Player object with the given propertie\n  return new Ps\n}\n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.speed = speed;\n    this.name = name;\n    this.damage = damage;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) {\n  // Create and return a new Player object with the given propertie\n  return new Pls\n}\n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.speed = speed;\n    this.name = name;\n    this.damage = damage;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) {\n  // Create and return a new Player object with the given propertie\n  return new Plas\n}\n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.speed = speed;\n    this.name = name;\n    this.damage = damage;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) {\n  // Create and return a new Player object with the given propertie\n  return new Plays\n}\n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.speed = speed;\n    this.name = name;\n    this.damage = damage;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) {\n  // Create and return a new Player object with the given propertie\n  return new Playes\n}\n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.speed = speed;\n    this.name = name;\n    this.damage = damage;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) {\n  // Create and return a new Player object with the given propertie\n  return new Players\n}\n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.speed = speed;\n    this.name = name;\n    this.damage = damage;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) {\n  // Create and return a new Player object with the given propertie\n  return new Player s\n}\n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.speed = speed;\n    this.name = name;\n    this.damage = damage;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) {\n  // Create and return a new Player object with the given propertie\n  return new Player ()s\n}\n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.speed = speed;\n    this.name = name;\n    this.damage = damage;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) {\n  // Create and return a new Player object with the given propertie\n  return new Player (=)s\n}\n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.speed = speed;\n    this.name = name;\n    this.damage = damage;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) {\n  // Create and return a new Player object with the given propertie\n  return new Player s\n}\n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.speed = speed;\n    this.name = name;\n    this.damage = damage;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) {\n  // Create and return a new Player object with the given propertie\n  return new Players\n}\n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.speed = speed;\n    this.name = name;\n    this.damage = damage;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) {\n  // Create and return a new Player object with the given propertie\n  return new Player ()s\n}\n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.speed = speed;\n    this.name = name;\n    this.damage = damage;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) {\n  // Create and return a new Player object with the given propertie\n  return new Player (h)s\n}\n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.speed = speed;\n    this.name = name;\n    this.damage = damage;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) {\n  // Create and return a new Player object with the given propertie\n  return new Player (he)s\n}\n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.speed = speed;\n    this.name = name;\n    this.damage = damage;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) {\n  // Create and return a new Player object with the given propertie\n  return new Player (hea)s\n}\n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.speed = speed;\n    this.name = name;\n    this.damage = damage;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) {\n  // Create and return a new Player object with the given propertie\n  return new Player (heal)s\n}\n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.speed = speed;\n    this.name = name;\n    this.damage = damage;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) {\n  // Create and return a new Player object with the given propertie\n  return new Player (healh)s\n}\n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.speed = speed;\n    this.name = name;\n    this.damage = damage;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) {\n  // Create and return a new Player object with the given propertie\n  return new Player (healt)s\n}\n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.speed = speed;\n    this.name = name;\n    this.damage = damage;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) {\n  // Create and return a new Player object with the given propertie\n  return new Player (health)s\n}\n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.speed = speed;\n    this.name = name;\n    this.damage = damage;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) {\n  // Create and return a new Player object with the given propertie\n  return new Player (health,)s\n}\n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.speed = speed;\n    this.name = name;\n    this.damage = damage;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) {\n  // Create and return a new Player object with the given propertie\n  return new Player (health, )s\n}\n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.speed = speed;\n    this.name = name;\n    this.damage = damage;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) {\n  // Create and return a new Player object with the given propertie\n  return new Player (health, w)s\n}\n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.speed = speed;\n    this.name = name;\n    this.damage = damage;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) {\n  // Create and return a new Player object with the given propertie\n  return new Player (health, we)s\n}\n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.speed = speed;\n    this.name = name;\n    this.damage = damage;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) {\n  // Create and return a new Player object with the given propertie\n  return new Player (health, wea)s\n}\n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.speed = speed;\n    this.name = name;\n    this.damage = damage;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) {\n  // Create and return a new Player object with the given propertie\n  return new Player (health, weap)s\n}\n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.speed = speed;\n    this.name = name;\n    this.damage = damage;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) {\n  // Create and return a new Player object with the given propertie\n  return new Player (health, weapo)s\n}\n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.speed = speed;\n    this.name = name;\n    this.damage = damage;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) {\n  // Create and return a new Player object with the given propertie\n  return new Player (health, weapon)s\n}\n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.speed = speed;\n    this.name = name;\n    this.damage = damage;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) {\n  // Create and return a new Player object with the given propertie\n  return new Player (health, weapon,)s\n}\n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.speed = speed;\n    this.name = name;\n    this.damage = damage;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) {\n  // Create and return a new Player object with the given propertie\n  return new Player (health, weapon, )s\n}\n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.speed = speed;\n    this.name = name;\n    this.damage = damage;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) {\n  // Create and return a new Player object with the given propertie\n  return new Player (health, weapon, s)s\n}\n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.speed = speed;\n    this.name = name;\n    this.damage = damage;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) {\n  // Create and return a new Player object with the given propertie\n  return new Player (health, weapon, sp)s\n}\n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.speed = speed;\n    this.name = name;\n    this.damage = damage;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) {\n  // Create and return a new Player object with the given propertie\n  return new Player (health, weapon, spe)s\n}\n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.speed = speed;\n    this.name = name;\n    this.damage = damage;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) {\n  // Create and return a new Player object with the given propertie\n  return new Player (health, weapon, spee)s\n}\n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.speed = speed;\n    this.name = name;\n    this.damage = damage;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) {\n  // Create and return a new Player object with the given propertie\n  return new Player (health, weapon, speed)s\n}\n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.speed = speed;\n    this.name = name;\n    this.damage = damage;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) {\n  // Create and return a new Player object with the given propertie\n  return new Player (health, weapon, speed,)s\n}\n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.speed = speed;\n    this.name = name;\n    this.damage = damage;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) {\n  // Create and return a new Player object with the given propertie\n  return new Player (health, weapon, speed, )s\n}\n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.speed = speed;\n    this.name = name;\n    this.damage = damage;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) {\n  // Create and return a new Player object with the given propertie\n  return new Player (health, weapon, speed, n)s\n}\n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.speed = speed;\n    this.name = name;\n    this.damage = damage;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) {\n  // Create and return a new Player object with the given propertie\n  return new Player (health, weapon, speed, na)s\n}\n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.speed = speed;\n    this.name = name;\n    this.damage = damage;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) {\n  // Create and return a new Player object with the given propertie\n  return new Player (health, weapon, speed, nam)s\n}\n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.speed = speed;\n    this.name = name;\n    this.damage = damage;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) {\n  // Create and return a new Player object with the given propertie\n  return new Player (health, weapon, speed, name)s\n}\n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.speed = speed;\n    this.name = name;\n    this.damage = damage;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) {\n  // Create and return a new Player object with the given propertie\n  return new Player (health, weapon, speed, namem)s\n}\n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.speed = speed;\n    this.name = name;\n    this.damage = damage;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) {\n  // Create and return a new Player object with the given propertie\n  return new Player (health, weapon, speed, name,)s\n}\n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.speed = speed;\n    this.name = name;\n    this.damage = damage;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) {\n  // Create and return a new Player object with the given propertie\n  return new Player (health, weapon, speed, name, )s\n}\n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.speed = speed;\n    this.name = name;\n    this.damage = damage;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) {\n  // Create and return a new Player object with the given propertie\n  return new Player (health, weapon, speed, name, d)s\n}\n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.speed = speed;\n    this.name = name;\n    this.damage = damage;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) {\n  // Create and return a new Player object with the given propertie\n  return new Player (health, weapon, speed, name, da)s\n}\n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.speed = speed;\n    this.name = name;\n    this.damage = damage;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) {\n  // Create and return a new Player object with the given propertie\n  return new Player (health, weapon, speed, name, dam)s\n}\n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.speed = speed;\n    this.name = name;\n    this.damage = damage;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) {\n  // Create and return a new Player object with the given propertie\n  return new Player (health, weapon, speed, name, dama)s\n}\n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.speed = speed;\n    this.name = name;\n    this.damage = damage;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) {\n  // Create and return a new Player object with the given propertie\n  return new Player (health, weapon, speed, name, damag)s\n}\n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.speed = speed;\n    this.name = name;\n    this.damage = damage;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) {\n  // Create and return a new Player object with the given propertie\n  return new Player (health, weapon, speed, name, damage)s\n}\n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damagegy {    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.speed = speed;\n    this.name = name;\n    this.damage = damage;\n)\n  \n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) {\n  // Create and return a new Player object with the given propertie\n  return new Player (health, weapon, speed, name, damage);s\n}\n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function simulateBattle(player1, player2) {\n  /* take two player objects and simulate them attacking each other\n   return an object with the updated health of both players after one round\n  example:  */\n}\n\nmodule.exports = simulateBattle;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex8-battle-simulation.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function simulateBattle(player1, player2) {\n  /* take two player objects and simulate them attacking each other\n   return an object with the updated health of both players after one round\n  example:  */\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = simulateBattle;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex8-battle-simulation.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function simulateBattle(player1, player2) {\n  /* take two player objects and simulate them attacking each other\n   return an object with the updated health of both players after one round\n  example:  */\n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = simulateBattle;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex8-battle-simulation.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function simulateBattle(player1, player2) {\n  /* take two player objects and simulate them attacking each other\n   return an object with the updated health of both players after one round\n  example:  */\n  \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = simulateBattle;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex8-battle-simulation.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function simulateBattle(player1, player2) {\n  /* take two player objects and simulate them attacking each other\n   return an object with the updated health of both players after one round\n  example:  */\n\n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = simulateBattle;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex8-battle-simulation.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function simulateBattle(player1, player2) {\n  /* take two player objects and simulate them attacking each other\n   return an object with the updated health of both players after one round\n  example:  */\n\n  P\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = simulateBattle;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex8-battle-simulation.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function simulateBattle(player1, player2) {\n  /* take two player objects and simulate them attacking each other\n   return an object with the updated health of both players after one round\n  example:  */\n\n  Pl\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = simulateBattle;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex8-battle-simulation.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function simulateBattle(player1, player2) {\n  /* take two player objects and simulate them attacking each other\n   return an object with the updated health of both players after one round\n  example:  */\n\n  Pla\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = simulateBattle;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex8-battle-simulation.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function simulateBattle(player1, player2) {\n  /* take two player objects and simulate them attacking each other\n   return an object with the updated health of both players after one round\n  example:  */\n\n  Play\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = simulateBattle;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex8-battle-simulation.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function simulateBattle(player1, player2) {\n  /* take two player objects and simulate them attacking each other\n   return an object with the updated health of both players after one round\n  example:  */\n\n  Playe\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = simulateBattle;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex8-battle-simulation.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function simulateBattle(player1, player2) {\n  /* take two player objects and simulate them attacking each other\n   return an object with the updated health of both players after one round\n  example:  */\n\n  Player\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = simulateBattle;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex8-battle-simulation.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function simulateBattle(player1, player2) {\n  /* take two player objects and simulate them attacking each other\n   return an object with the updated health of both players after one round\n  example:  */\n\n  Player1\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = simulateBattle;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex8-battle-simulation.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function simulateBattle(player1, player2) {\n  /* take two player objects and simulate them attacking each other\n   return an object with the updated health of both players after one round\n  example:  */\n\n  Player1 \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = simulateBattle;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex8-battle-simulation.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function simulateBattle(player1, player2) {\n  /* take two player objects and simulate them attacking each other\n   return an object with the updated health of both players after one round\n  example:  */\n\n  Player\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = simulateBattle;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex8-battle-simulation.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function simulateBattle(player1, player2) {\n  /* take two player objects and simulate them attacking each other\n   return an object with the updated health of both players after one round\n  example:  */\n\n  Playe\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = simulateBattle;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex8-battle-simulation.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function simulateBattle(player1, player2) {\n  /* take two player objects and simulate them attacking each other\n   return an object with the updated health of both players after one round\n  example:  */\n\n  Play\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = simulateBattle;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex8-battle-simulation.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function simulateBattle(player1, player2) {\n  /* take two player objects and simulate them attacking each other\n   return an object with the updated health of both players after one round\n  example:  */\n\n  Pla\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = simulateBattle;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex8-battle-simulation.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function simulateBattle(player1, player2) {\n  /* take two player objects and simulate them attacking each other\n   return an object with the updated health of both players after one round\n  example:  */\n\n  Pl\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = simulateBattle;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex8-battle-simulation.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function simulateBattle(player1, player2) {\n  /* take two player objects and simulate them attacking each other\n   return an object with the updated health of both players after one round\n  example:  */\n\n  P\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = simulateBattle;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex8-battle-simulation.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function simulateBattle(player1, player2) {\n  /* take two player objects and simulate them attacking each other\n   return an object with the updated health of both players after one round\n  example:  */\n\n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = simulateBattle;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex8-battle-simulation.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function simulateBattle(player1, player2) {\n  /* take two player objects and simulate them attacking each other\n   return an object with the updated health of both players after one round\n  example:  */\n\n  p\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = simulateBattle;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex8-battle-simulation.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function simulateBattle(player1, player2) {\n  /* take two player objects and simulate them attacking each other\n   return an object with the updated health of both players after one round\n  example:  */\n\n  pl\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = simulateBattle;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex8-battle-simulation.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function simulateBattle(player1, player2) {\n  /* take two player objects and simulate them attacking each other\n   return an object with the updated health of both players after one round\n  example:  */\n\n  pla\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = simulateBattle;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex8-battle-simulation.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function simulateBattle(player1, player2) {\n  /* take two player objects and simulate them attacking each other\n   return an object with the updated health of both players after one round\n  example:  */\n\n  play\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = simulateBattle;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex8-battle-simulation.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function simulateBattle(player1, player2) {\n  /* take two player objects and simulate them attacking each other\n   return an object with the updated health of both players after one round\n  example:  */\n\n  playe\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = simulateBattle;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex8-battle-simulation.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function simulateBattle(player1, player2) {\n  /* take two player objects and simulate them attacking each other\n   return an object with the updated health of both players after one round\n  example:  */\n\n  player\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = simulateBattle;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex8-battle-simulation.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function simulateBattle(player1, player2) {\n  /* take two player objects and simulate them attacking each other\n   return an object with the updated health of both players after one round\n  example:  */\n\n  player1\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = simulateBattle;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex8-battle-simulation.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function simulateBattle(player1, player2) {\n  /* take two player objects and simulate them attacking each other\n   return an object with the updated health of both players after one round\n  example:  */\n\n  player1 \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = simulateBattle;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex8-battle-simulation.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damage) {\n    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.speed = speed;\n    this.name = name;\n    this.damage = damage;\n  }\n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) {\n  // Create and return a new Player object with the given properties\n  return new Player (health, weapon, speed, name, damage);\n}\n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function simulateBattle(player1, player2) {\n  /* take two player objects and simulate them attacking each other\n   return an object with the updated health of both players after one round\n  example:  */\n\n  player1 \n}\n\nmodule.exports = simulateBattle;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex8-battle-simulation.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function simulateBattle(player1, player2) {\n  /* take two player objects and simulate them attacking each other\n   return an object with the updated health of both players after one round\n  example:  */\n\n  player1 ()\n}\n\nmodule.exports = simulateBattle;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex8-battle-simulation.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function simulateBattle(player1, player2) {\n  /* take two player objects and simulate them attacking each other\n   return an object with the updated health of both players after one round\n  example:  */\n\n  player1 (h)\n}\n\nmodule.exports = simulateBattle;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex8-battle-simulation.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function simulateBattle(player1, player2) {\n  /* take two player objects and simulate them attacking each other\n   return an object with the updated health of both players after one round\n  example:  */\n\n  player1 (he)\n}\n\nmodule.exports = simulateBattle;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex8-battle-simulation.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function simulateBattle(player1, player2) {\n  /* take two player objects and simulate them attacking each other\n   return an object with the updated health of both players after one round\n  example:  */\n\n  player1 (hea)\n}\n\nmodule.exports = simulateBattle;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex8-battle-simulation.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function simulateBattle(player1, player2) {\n  /* take two player objects and simulate them attacking each other\n   return an object with the updated health of both players after one round\n  example:  */\n\n  player1 (h)\n}\n\nmodule.exports = simulateBattle;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex8-battle-simulation.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function simulateBattle(player1, player2) {\n  /* take two player objects and simulate them attacking each other\n   return an object with the updated health of both players after one round\n  example:  */\n\n  player1 ()\n}\n\nmodule.exports = simulateBattle;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex8-battle-simulation.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function simulateBattle(player1, player2) {\n  /* take two player objects and simulate them attacking each other\n   return an object with the updated health of both players after one round\n  example:  */\n\n  player1 (r)\n}\n\nmodule.exports = simulateBattle;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex8-battle-simulation.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function simulateBattle(player1, player2) {\n  /* take two player objects and simulate them attacking each other\n   return an object with the updated health of both players after one round\n  example:  */\n\n  player1 (h)\n}\n\nmodule.exports = simulateBattle;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex8-battle-simulation.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function simulateBattle(player1, player2) {\n  /* take two player objects and simulate them attacking each other\n   return an object with the updated health of both players after one round\n  example:  */\n\n  player1 (he)\n}\n\nmodule.exports = simulateBattle;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex8-battle-simulation.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function simulateBattle(player1, player2) {\n  /* take two player objects and simulate them attacking each other\n   return an object with the updated health of both players after one round\n  example:  */\n\n  player1 (hea)\n}\n\nmodule.exports = simulateBattle;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex8-battle-simulation.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function simulateBattle(player1, player2) {\n  /* take two player objects and simulate them attacking each other\n   return an object with the updated health of both players after one round\n  example:  */\n\n  player1 (heal)\n}\n\nmodule.exports = simulateBattle;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex8-battle-simulation.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function simulateBattle(player1, player2) {\n  /* take two player objects and simulate them attacking each other\n   return an object with the updated health of both players after one round\n  example:  */\n\n  player1 (healt)\n}\n\nmodule.exports = simulateBattle;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex8-battle-simulation.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function simulateBattle(player1, player2) {\n  /* take two player objects and simulate them attacking each other\n   return an object with the updated health of both players after one round\n  example:  */\n\n  player1 (health)\n}\n\nmodule.exports = simulateBattle;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex8-battle-simulation.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damage) {\n    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.speed = speed;\n    this.name = name;\n    this.damage = damage;\n  }\n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) {\n  // Create and return a new Player object with the given properties\n  return new Player (health, weapon, speed, name, damage);\n}\n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function simulateBattle(player1, player2) {\n  /* take two player objects and simulate them attacking each other\n   return an object with the updated health of both players after one round\n  example:  */\n\n  player1 (health,)\n}\n\nmodule.exports = simulateBattle;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex8-battle-simulation.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function simulateBattle(player1, player2) {\n  /* take two player objects and simulate them attacking each other\n   return an object with the updated health of both players after one round\n  example:  */\n\n  player1 (health, )\n}\n\nmodule.exports = simulateBattle;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex8-battle-simulation.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function simulateBattle(player1, player2) {\n  /* take two player objects and simulate them attacking each other\n   return an object with the updated health of both players after one round\n  example:  */\n\n  player1 (health, d)\n}\n\nmodule.exports = simulateBattle;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex8-battle-simulation.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function simulateBattle(player1, player2) {\n  /* take two player objects and simulate them attacking each other\n   return an object with the updated health of both players after one round\n  example:  */\n\n  player1 (health, da)\n}\n\nmodule.exports = simulateBattle;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex8-battle-simulation.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function simulateBattle(player1, player2) {\n  /* take two player objects and simulate them attacking each other\n   return an object with the updated health of both players after one round\n  example:  */\n\n  player1 (health, dam)\n}\n\nmodule.exports = simulateBattle;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex8-battle-simulation.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function simulateBattle(player1, player2) {\n  /* take two player objects and simulate them attacking each other\n   return an object with the updated health of both players after one round\n  example:  */\n\n  player1 (health, dama)\n}\n\nmodule.exports = simulateBattle;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex8-battle-simulation.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function simulateBattle(player1, player2) {\n  /* take two player objects and simulate them attacking each other\n   return an object with the updated health of both players after one round\n  example:  */\n\n  player1 (health, damag)\n}\n\nmodule.exports = simulateBattle;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex8-battle-simulation.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function simulateBattle(player1, player2) {\n  /* take two player objects and simulate them attacking each other\n   return an object with the updated health of both players after one round\n  example:  */\n\n  player1 (health, damagg)\n}\n\nmodule.exports = simulateBattle;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex8-battle-simulation.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function simulateBattle(player1, player2) {\n  /* take two player objects and simulate them attacking each other\n   return an object with the updated health of both players after one round\n  example:  */\n\n  player1 (health, damaghg)\n}\n\nmodule.exports = simulateBattle;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex8-battle-simulation.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function simulateBattle(player1, player2) {\n  /* take two player objects and simulate them attacking each other\n   return an object with the updated health of both players after one round\n  example:  */\n\n  player1 (health, damagheg)\n}\n\nmodule.exports = simulateBattle;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex8-battle-simulation.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function simulateBattle(player1, player2) {\n  /* take two player objects and simulate them attacking each other\n   return an object with the updated health of both players after one round\n  example:  */\n\n  player1 (health, damagg)\n}\n\nmodule.exports = simulateBattle;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex8-battle-simulation.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function simulateBattle(player1, player2) {\n  /* take two player objects and simulate them attacking each other\n   return an object with the updated health of both players after one round\n  example:  */\n\n  player1 (health, damageg)\n}\n\nmodule.exports = simulateBattle;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex8-battle-simulation.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function simulateBattle(player1, player2) {\n  /* take two player objects and simulate them attacking each other\n   return an object with the updated health of both players after one round\n  example:  */\n\n  player1 (health, damageag)\n}\n\nmodule.exports = simulateBattle;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex8-battle-simulation.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function simulateBattle(player1, player2) {\n  /* take two player objects and simulate them attacking each other\n   return an object with the updated health of both players after one round\n  example:  */\n\n  player1 (health, damagg)\n}\n\nmodule.exports = simulateBattle;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex8-battle-simulation.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function simulateBattle(player1, player2) {\n  /* take two player objects and simulate them attacking each other\n   return an object with the updated health of both players after one round\n  example:  */\n\n  player1 (health, damag)\n}\n\nmodule.exports = simulateBattle;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex8-battle-simulation.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function simulateBattle(player1, player2) {\n  /* take two player objects and simulate them attacking each other\n   return an object with the updated health of both players after one round\n  example:  */\n\n  player1 (health, damg)\n}\n\nmodule.exports = simulateBattle;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex8-battle-simulation.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function simulateBattle(player1, player2) {\n  /* take two player objects and simulate them attacking each other\n   return an object with the updated health of both players after one round\n  example:  */\n\n  player1 (health, dag)\n}\n\nmodule.exports = simulateBattle;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex8-battle-simulation.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function simulateBattle(player1, player2) {\n  /* take two player objects and simulate them attacking each other\n   return an object with the updated health of both players after one round\n  example:  */\n\n  player1 (health, dg)\n}\n\nmodule.exports = simulateBattle;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex8-battle-simulation.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function simulateBattle(player1, player2) {\n  /* take two player objects and simulate them attacking each other\n   return an object with the updated health of both players after one round\n  example:  */\n\n  player1 (health, g)\n}\n\nmodule.exports = simulateBattle;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex8-battle-simulation.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function simulateBattle(player1, player2) {\n  /* take two player objects and simulate them attacking each other\n   return an object with the updated health of both players after one round\n  example:  */\n\n  player1 (health,g)\n}\n\nmodule.exports = simulateBattle;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex8-battle-simulation.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function simulateBattle(player1, player2) {\n  /* take two player objects and simulate them attacking each other\n   return an object with the updated health of both players after one round\n  example:  */\n\n  player1 (healthg)\n}\n\nmodule.exports = simulateBattle;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex8-battle-simulation.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n\n  constructor(health, weapon, speed, name, damage) {\n    this.health = health;\n    this.weapon = weapon;\n    this.speed = speed;\n    this.name = name;\n    this.damage = damage;\n  }\n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) {\n  // Create and return a new Player object with the given properties\n  return new Player (health, weapon, speed, name, damage);\n}\n\n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function simulateBattle(player1, player2) {\n  /* take two player objects and simulate them attacking each other\n   return an object with the updated health of both players after one round\n  example:  */\n\n  player1 (health)\n}\n\nmodule.exports = simulateBattle;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex8-battle-simulation.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function simulateBattle(player1, player2) {\n  /* take two player objects and simulate them attacking each other\n   return an object with the updated health of both players after one round\n  example:  */\n\n  r\n}\n\nmodule.exports = simulateBattle;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex8-battle-simulation.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function simulateBattle(player1, player2) {\n  /* take two player objects and simulate them attacking each other\n   return an object with the updated health of both players after one round\n  example:  */\n\n  rt\n}\n\nmodule.exports = simulateBattle;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex8-battle-simulation.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function simulateBattle(player1, player2) {\n  /* take two player objects and simulate them attacking each other\n   return an object with the updated health of both players after one round\n  example:  */\n\n  rte\n}\n\nmodule.exports = simulateBattle;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex8-battle-simulation.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function simulateBattle(player1, player2) {\n  /* take two player objects and simulate them attacking each other\n   return an object with the updated health of both players after one round\n  example:  */\n\n  rteu\n}\n\nmodule.exports = simulateBattle;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex8-battle-simulation.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function simulateBattle(player1, player2) {\n  /* take two player objects and simulate them attacking each other\n   return an object with the updated health of both players after one round\n  example:  */\n\n  rteue\n}\n\nmodule.exports = simulateBattle;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex8-battle-simulation.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function simulateBattle(player1, player2) {\n  /* take two player objects and simulate them attacking each other\n   return an object with the updated health of both players after one round\n  example:  */\n\n  rteuen\n}\n\nmodule.exports = simulateBattle;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex8-battle-simulation.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function simulateBattle(player1, player2) {\n  /* take two player objects and simulate them attacking each other\n   return an object with the updated health of both players after one round\n  example:  */\n\n  rteu\n}\n\nmodule.exports = simulateBattle;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex8-battle-simulation.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function simulateBattle(player1, player2) {\n  /* take two player objects and simulate them attacking each other\n   return an object with the updated health of both players after one round\n  example:  */\n\n  rte\n}\n\nmodule.exports = simulateBattle;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex8-battle-simulation.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function simulateBattle(player1, player2) {\n  /* take two player objects and simulate them attacking each other\n   return an object with the updated health of both players after one round\n  example:  */\n\n  rt\n}\n\nmodule.exports = simulateBattle;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex8-battle-simulation.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function simulateBattle(player1, player2) {\n  /* take two player objects and simulate them attacking each other\n   return an object with the updated health of both players after one round\n  example:  */\n\n  r\n}\n\nmodule.exports = simulateBattle;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex8-battle-simulation.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function simulateBattle(player1, player2) {\n  /* take two player objects and simulate them attacking each other\n   return an object with the updated health of both players after one round\n  example:  */\n\n  re\n}\n\nmodule.exports = simulateBattle;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex8-battle-simulation.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function simulateBattle(player1, player2) {\n  /* take two player objects and simulate them attacking each other\n   return an object with the updated health of both players after one round\n  example:  */\n\n  ret\n}\n\nmodule.exports = simulateBattle;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex8-battle-simulation.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function simulateBattle(player1, player2) {\n  /* take two player objects and simulate them attacking each other\n   return an object with the updated health of both players after one round\n  example:  */\n\n  retu\n}\n\nmodule.exports = simulateBattle;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex8-battle-simulation.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function simulateBattle(player1, player2) {\n  /* take two player objects and simulate them attacking each other\n   return an object with the updated health of both players after one round\n  example:  */\n\n  retur\n}\n\nmodule.exports = simulateBattle;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex8-battle-simulation.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function simulateBattle(player1, player2) {\n  /* take two player objects and simulate them attacking each other\n   return an object with the updated health of both players after one round\n  example:  */\n\n  return\n}\n\nmodule.exports = simulateBattle;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex8-battle-simulation.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function simulateBattle(player1, player2) {\n  /* take two player objects and simulate them attacking each other\n   return an object with the updated health of both players after one round\n  example:  */\n\n  return \n}\n\nmodule.exports = simulateBattle;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex8-battle-simulation.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function simulateBattle(player1, player2) {\n  /* take two player objects and simulate them attacking each other\n   return an object with the updated health of both players after one round\n  example:  */\n\n  return ()\n}\n\nmodule.exports = simulateBattle;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex8-battle-simulation.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function simulateBattle(player1, player2) {\n  /* take two player objects and simulate them attacking each other\n   return an object with the updated health of both players after one round\n  example:  */\n\n  return (o)\n}\n\nmodule.exports = simulateBattle;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex8-battle-simulation.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function simulateBattle(player1, player2) {\n  /* take two player objects and simulate them attacking each other\n   return an object with the updated health of both players after one round\n  example:  */\n\n  return (ob)\n}\n\nmodule.exports = simulateBattle;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex8-battle-simulation.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function simulateBattle(player1, player2) {\n  /* take two player objects and simulate them attacking each other\n   return an object with the updated health of both players after one round\n  example:  */\n\n  return ()\n}\n\nmodule.exports = simulateBattle;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex8-battle-simulation.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function simulateBattle(player1, player2) {\n  /* take two player objects and simulate them attacking each other\n   return an object with the updated health of both players after one round\n  example:  */\n\n  return \n}\n\nmodule.exports = simulateBattle;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex8-battle-simulation.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function simulateBattle(player1, player2) {\n  /* take two player objects and simulate them attacking each other\n   return an object with the updated health of both players after one round\n  example:  */\n\n  return {}\n}\n\nmodule.exports = simulateBattle;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex8-battle-simulation.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function simulateBattle(player1, player2) {\n  /* take two player objects and simulate them attacking each other\n   return an object with the updated health of both players after one round\n  example:  */\n\n  return {\n    player1player1.health - player2.damage, player2.health - player1.damage\n  }\n}\n\nmodule.exports = simulateBattle;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex8-battle-simulation.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function simulateBattle(player1, player2) {\n  /* take two player objects and simulate them attacking each other\n   return an object with the updated health of both players after one round\n  example:  */\n\n  return {\n    player1Hplayer1.health - player2.damage, player2.health - player1.damage\n  }\n}\n\nmodule.exports = simulateBattle;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex8-battle-simulation.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function simulateBattle(player1, player2) {\n  /* take two player objects and simulate them attacking each other\n   return an object with the updated health of both players after one round\n  example:  */\n\n  return {\n    player1HPplayer1.health - player2.damage, player2.health - player1.damage\n  }\n}\n\nmodule.exports = simulateBattle;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex8-battle-simulation.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function simulateBattle(player1, player2) {\n  /* take two player objects and simulate them attacking each other\n   return an object with the updated health of both players after one round\n  example:  */\n\n  return {\n    player1HP[player1.health - player2.damage, player2.health - player1.damage\n  }\n}\n\nmodule.exports = simulateBattle;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex8-battle-simulation.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function simulateBattle(player1, player2) {\n  /* take two player objects and simulate them attacking each other\n   return an object with the updated health of both players after one round\n  example:  */\n\n  return {\n    player1HP;player1.health - player2.damage, player2.health - player1.damage\n  }\n}\n\nmodule.exports = simulateBattle;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex8-battle-simulation.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function simulateBattle(player1, player2) {\n  /* take two player objects and simulate them attacking each other\n   return an object with the updated health of both players after one round\n  example:  */\n\n  return {\n    player1HPplayer1.health - player2.damage, player2.health - player1.damage\n  }\n}\n\nmodule.exports = simulateBattle;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex8-battle-simulation.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function simulateBattle(player1, player2) {\n  /* take two player objects and simulate them attacking each other\n   return an object with the updated health of both players after one round\n  example:  */\n\n  return {\n    player1HP:player1.health - player2.damage, player2.health - player1.damage\n  }\n}\n\nmodule.exports = simulateBattle;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex8-battle-simulation.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function simulateBattle(player1, player2) {\n  /* take two player objects and simulate them attacking each other\n   return an object with the updated health of both players after one round\n  example:  */\n\n  return {\n    player1HP:player1.health - player2.damage, pplayer2.health - player1.damage\n  }\n}\n\nmodule.exports = simulateBattle;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex8-battle-simulation.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function simulateBattle(player1, player2) {\n  /* take two player objects and simulate them attacking each other\n   return an object with the updated health of both players after one round\n  example:  */\n\n  return {\n    player1HP:player1.health - player2.damage, plplayer2.health - player1.damage\n  }\n}\n\nmodule.exports = simulateBattle;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex8-battle-simulation.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function simulateBattle(player1, player2) {\n  /* take two player objects and simulate them attacking each other\n   return an object with the updated health of both players after one round\n  example:  */\n\n  return {\n    player1HP:player1.health - player2.damage, plaplayer2.health - player1.damage\n  }\n}\n\nmodule.exports = simulateBattle;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex8-battle-simulation.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function simulateBattle(player1, player2) {\n  /* take two player objects and simulate them attacking each other\n   return an object with the updated health of both players after one round\n  example:  */\n\n  return {\n    player1HP:player1.health - player2.damage, playplayer2.health - player1.damage\n  }\n}\n\nmodule.exports = simulateBattle;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex8-battle-simulation.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function simulateBattle(player1, player2) {\n  /* take two player objects and simulate them attacking each other\n   return an object with the updated health of both players after one round\n  example:  */\n\n  return {\n    player1HP:player1.health - player2.damage, playeplayer2.health - player1.damage\n  }\n}\n\nmodule.exports = simulateBattle;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex8-battle-simulation.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function simulateBattle(player1, player2) {\n  /* take two player objects and simulate them attacking each other\n   return an object with the updated health of both players after one round\n  example:  */\n\n  return {\n    player1HP:player1.health - player2.damage, playerplayer2.health - player1.damage\n  }\n}\n\nmodule.exports = simulateBattle;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex8-battle-simulation.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function simulateBattle(player1, player2) {\n  /* take two player objects and simulate them attacking each other\n   return an object with the updated health of both players after one round\n  example:  */\n\n  return {\n    player1HP:player1.health - player2.damage, player2player2.health - player1.damage\n  }\n}\n\nmodule.exports = simulateBattle;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex8-battle-simulation.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function simulateBattle(player1, player2) {\n  /* take two player objects and simulate them attacking each other\n   return an object with the updated health of both players after one round\n  example:  */\n\n  return {\n    player1HP:player1.health - player2.damage, player2Hplayer2.health - player1.damage\n  }\n}\n\nmodule.exports = simulateBattle;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex8-battle-simulation.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function simulateBattle(player1, player2) {\n  /* take two player objects and simulate them attacking each other\n   return an object with the updated health of both players after one round\n  example:  */\n\n  return {\n    player1HP:player1.health - player2.damage, player2HPplayer2.health - player1.damage\n  }\n}\n\nmodule.exports = simulateBattle;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex8-battle-simulation.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function simulateBattle(player1, player2) {\n  /* take two player objects and simulate them attacking each other\n   return an object with the updated health of both players after one round\n  example:  */\n\n  return {\n    player1HP:player1.health - player2.damage, player2HP;player2.health - player1.damage\n  }\n}\n\nmodule.exports = simulateBattle;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex8-battle-simulation.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function simulateBattle(player1, player2) {\n  /* take two player objects and simulate them attacking each other\n   return an object with the updated health of both players after one round\n  example:  */\n\n  return {\n    player1HP:player1.health - player2.damage, player2HP;=player2.health - player1.damage\n  }\n}\n\nmodule.exports = simulateBattle;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex8-battle-simulation.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function simulateBattle(player1, player2) {\n  /* take two player objects and simulate them attacking each other\n   return an object with the updated health of both players after one round\n  example:  */\n\n  return {\n    player1HP:player1.health - player2.damage, player2HPplayer2.health - player1.damage\n  }\n}\n\nmodule.exports = simulateBattle;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex8-battle-simulation.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function simulateBattle(player1, player2) {\n  /* take two player objects and simulate them attacking each other\n   return an object with the updated health of both players after one round\n  example:  */\n\n  return {\n    player1HP:player1.health - player2.damage, player2HP:player2.health - player1.damage\n  }\n}\n\nmodule.exports = simulateBattle;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex8-battle-simulation.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const createLyrics = require('../../exercises/hard/ex5-template-lyrics');\n\ndescribe('Template Literals Lyrics function', () => {\n  test('should create lyrics using template literals', () => {\n    const songData = {\n      artist: 'Test Artist',\n      title: 'Test Song',\n      verse: 'This is a test verse',\n      chorus: 'This is a test chorus'\n    };\n    \n    const result = createLyrics(songData);\n    \n    expect(result).toContain(songData.artist);\n    expect(result).toContain(songData.title);\n    expect(result).toContain(songData.verse);\n    expect(result).toContain(songData.chorus);\n    \n    const functionString = createLyrics.toString();\n    expect(functionString).toMatch(/`.*\\$.*`/s);\n  });\n});\n","file":"tests/hard/ex5.test.js","language":"javascript"}
= require('../../exercises/hard/ex7-player-class');\n\ndescribe('Player Class', () => {\n  test('should create a player with all required properties', () => {\n    const player = new Player('Hero', 100, 'Sword', 10, 25);\n    \n    expect(player.name).toBe('Hero');\n    expect(player.health).toBe(100);\n    expect(player.weapon).toBe('Sword');\n    expect(player.speed).toBe(10);\n    expect(player.damage).toBe(25);\n  });\n  \n  test('createPlayer function should return a Player instance', () => {\n    const player = createPlayer('Villain', 80, 'Axe', 8, 30);\n    \n    expect(player instanceof Player).toBe(true);\n    expect(player.name).toBe('Villain');\n    expect(player.health).toBe(80);\n    expect(player.weapon).toBe('Axe');\n    expect(player.speed).toBe(8);\n    expect(player.damage).toBe(30);\n  });\n});\n","file":"tests/hard/ex7.test.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const simulateBattle = require('../../exercises/hard/ex8-battle-simulation');\n\ndescribe('Battle Simulation function', () => {\n  test('should reduce health of both players based on damage', () => {\n    const player1 = ;\n    const player2 = ;\n    \n    const result = simulateBattle(player1, player2);\n    \n    expect(result).toHaveProperty('player1Health');\n    expect(result).toHaveProperty('player2Health');\n    expect(result.player1Health).toBe(85); // 100 - 15\n    expect(result.player2Health).toBe(60); // 80 - 20\n  });\n});\n","file":"tests/hard/ex8.test.js","language":"javascript"}